我不想燃烧这个世界
I don't want to set the world on fire
我只是想要
I just want to start
点燃你心中的火焰
A flame in your heart
我的心中只有一个愿望
In my heart I have but one desire
那就是你
And that one is you
别人无可替代
No other will do
我不想获得别人的赞赏
I've lost all ambition for worldly acclaim
我只想成为你所爱的人
I just want to be the one you love
只要你承认你也爱我
And with your admission that you feel the same
我就实现了梦想
I'll have reached the goal I'm dreaming of
相信我
Believe me!
我不想燃烧这个世界
I don't want to set the world on fire
我只是想要
I just want to start
点燃你心中的火焰
A flame in your heart
我不想燃烧这个世界 亲爱的
I don't wanna set the world on fire, honey
我是如此地爱你
I love ya too much
我只是想要点燃
I just wanna start a great big flame
你心中的那团大火
down in your heart
你看
You see
在我的内心深处
Way down inside of me
亲爱的我只有一个愿望
Darlin' I have only one desire
那就是你
And that one desire is you
没人能替代你在我心中的位置
And I know nobody else ain't gonna do
我无心获得别人的赞赏
I've lost all ambition for wordly acclaim
我只想成为你所爱的人
I just want to be the one you love
只要你承认你也爱我
And with your admission that you feel the same
我就实现了梦想
I'll have reached the goal I'm dreaming of
相信我
Believe me
我不想燃烧这个世界
I don't want to set the world on fire
我只是想要
I just want to start
点燃你心中的火焰
A flame in your heart
AMV BGM:
I Don't Want To Set The World On Fire by The Ink Spots
我也想要吃胡萝卜咕哩
咕哩咕哩
AMV，歌词字幕:
Bolshevik0
胡萝卜 好好吃哦咕哩
卡斯 拉比 连婆婆也
片尾对话字幕:
原版繁中字幕
到底怎么回事
我想去地球参观一下耶
素材出处:
光能使者E34 E38 E39 E40 E41
我们中了月球的抽奖呀
我想要那个胡萝卜咕哩
那么肉就由我吃了
啊 肉是我先看上的耶
那用公平的抽签方式决定
抽签才不公平呢
真吵呀 两个人都来这了 能不能别吵啊
谢谢观看！
妈妈 看起来我的冒险还没完呀